I have a list of over 1000 post ideas that grows every single day and I don't have to do any
research for it. This is honestly my gold mine that I use before filming any content and the reason
it works so well is because these ideas aren't coming from trends, chai chibi tea or guesswork,
they're coming directly from my audience the exact moment they decide to follow me.
Let me show you how I set this up. Inside Minichat go to automations and select say hi to new followers.
This will automatically send a DM to somebody after they follow you. You can customize the timing
it sends out and the message itself. Now instead of just saying like hey thanks for the follow,
we send them a message where they could fill out a form with just their name handle and what they're
currently struggling with as a content creator. There is a million different ways you can optimize
this initial outreach message but this is just the way that my team and I have this set up right now.
This is insanely invaluable for anyone to have because it's real time insight into your followers
minds what they're actively struggling with the moment they press that follow button while you're
still top of mind. It's those moments that you don't want to miss that will give you clearer
direction than any sort of brainstorming session would. The number one automation platform where
you can automatically reply to comments, DMs, collect emails and even remind commenters to follow you.
If you want to build your own never ending list of content ideas directly from your audience,
comment connect 30 and I'll send you the link where you could try Minichat Pro for free for 30 days.